<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Admin</string>
    <string name="Q1">In order to understand your level of self-discovery and purpose in life, explain where you see yourself 10 years from now.</string>
    <string name="Q2">One criteria to participate in the YIL Fellowship is to have a hard skill (specialized skill). What is your hard skill? Briefly narrate your journey through acquiring it and how you have changed the world or intend to change the world with it.</string>
    <string name="Q3">Answer one of the following questions intended to test how well you know your discipline and field of study: • Explain the importance of your discipline in today’s society. • What do you think the industry will be like in the next 10 years ? • What are the most important issues your field is facing today ?</string>
    <string name="Q4">To test your skills at problem-solving and check how up-to-date you are on current issues, kindly answer any one of the following questions: • What do you consider to be the single most important societal problem in your country? Why? • If you had the authority to change your District/ Region/ State in a positive way, what specific changes would you make? • Pick a controversial problem in your country and suggest a solution.</string>
    <string name="Q5">In order to understand your leadership skills, kindly answer any one of the following questions: • Describe how you have demonstrated leadership ability both in and out of school. • Discuss a special attribute or accomplishment that sets you apart. • Describe your most meaningful achievements and how they relate to your future goals.</string>
    <string name="Q6">To test your understanding of the power of leverage, answer one of the following: • Pick an experience from your own life and explain how it has influenced your development. • Who in your life has been your biggest influence and why? • How has your family background affected the way you see the world? • Choose a book that has affected you deeply and explain why.</string>
</resources>